[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the lowest point in Europe?", "correct_answer": "The Caspian Sea", "incorrect_answers": ["Comedy clubs  in Germany", "Gabo de Roca", "Gavdos"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these cities was established first?", "correct_answer": "Madrid (Spain)", "incorrect_answers": ["New York City (New York)", "Copenhagen (Denmark)", "Boston (Massachusetts)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which statement about the emu and the kangaroo is not true?", "correct_answer": "Both are indigenous only to Australia.", "incorrect_answers": ["Both are on the national emblem of Australia.", "Both are incapable of flying.", "Both are incapable of  walking backwards."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following best describes heavy water?", "correct_answer": "Water with several isotopes of hydrogen", "incorrect_answers": ["Polluted water", "Water carrying silt down a river", "Water loaded with fluorides"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This multifunctional facility is located at 225 West Douglas, Wichita, Kansas.", "correct_answer": "Century II Convention center", "incorrect_answers": ["Exploration Place", "None of these", "Hyatt hotel"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which character from the 1984 horror film A Nightmare on Elm Street was the first to die?", "correct_answer": "Tina", "incorrect_answers": ["Glen", "Nancy", "Rod"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the second host of the Tonight Show?", "correct_answer": "Jack Paar", "incorrect_answers": ["Johnny Carson", "Steve Allen", "Jay Leno"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is the brightest star in the winter night sky of the northern hemisphere?", "correct_answer": "Sirius", "incorrect_answers": ["Procyon", "Strebe", "Aldeberan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What three things do rock stars get to have according to a freecreditreport.com commercial?", "correct_answer": "champagne, caviar, exotic cars", "incorrect_answers": ["champagn, credit cards, exotic cards", "cramping, Viagra, little scars", "campaigns, caviar, cattle cars"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Point Break, during the final escape, Bodhi wants the pilot to fly to what Mexican town?", "correct_answer": "San Felipe", "incorrect_answers": ["San Felix", "San Fernando", "San Francisco"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which word refers to the sound peacocks make?", "correct_answer": "Scream", "incorrect_answers": ["Squill", "Squeak", "Squall"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When Seth, one of the main characters in the movie Superbad, was younger, he had an obsession with drawing what?", "correct_answer": "Penises", "incorrect_answers": ["Stars", "Hearts", "Butts"]}]